I'm still unnecessarily conscious about how choosing myself makes other people feel.
And then I try not to feel bad about it or I try to candy coat it in a way so that you don't feel hurt.
I spent the entirety of my life up until like, let's say the last year and a half, feeding emotional stray cats.
And so people expect certain things of me because I've always given it because I never put myself first.
Yeah.
You choose yourself.
They get upset.
And that makes me feel bad.
But I'm still like, yo, I can't.
I know you want me to do that thing, but I can't.
I know you want me to hire you for the thing, but I don't think you're prepared.
And it's just going to f*** up my production if I bring you on.
So I can't.
Even in the professional space.
Especially in the professional space.
That's where I get taxed the most.
I don't feel like people tax me in the professional, but in the personal they tax me.
I don't get taxed that much in personal, but then I also, I have friends in quadrants.
Most of anything anybody needs of me is in a professional capacity.